[
    {
        "Question": "Who was drafted first overall in 1984?",
        "A1": "Wayne Gretzky",
        "A2": "Bobby Orr",
        "A3": "Bobby Hull",
        "A4": "Mario Lemieux",
        "Answer": "Mario Lemieux"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Bobby Orr holds the record for most consecutive Norris Trophies. How many did he win consecutively?",
        "A1": "6",
        "A2": "7",
        "A3": "8",
        "A4": "9",
        "Answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many minutes is a minor penalty?",
        "A1": "2",
        "A2": "4",
        "A3": "5",
        "A4": "10",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How long is an NHL ice rink?",
        "A1": "200ft",
        "A2": "150ft",
        "A3": "100yds",
        "A4": "25yds",
        "Answer": "200ft"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is Detroit's team name?",
        "A1": "Red Wings",
        "A2": "Penguins",
        "A3": "Oilers",
        "A4": "Blackhawks",
        "Answer": "Red Wings"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What player is known as 'Moose'",
        "A1": "Mark Messier",
        "A2": "Bobby Orr",
        "A3": "Jeff Skinner",
        "A4": "Bobby Hull",
        "Answer": "Mark Messier"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who were the Broad Street Bullies?",
        "A1": "Philadelphia Flyers",
        "A2": "Boston Bruins",
        "A3": "New York Rangers",
        "A4": "Chicago Blackhawks",
        "Answer": "Philadelphia Flyers"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who was the last team to win back to back Stanley Cups?",
        "A1": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
        "A2": "Washington Capitals",
        "A3": "Chicago Blackhawks",
        "A4": "Dallas Start",
        "Answer": "Pittsburgh Penguins"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who won the Stanley Cup in 2000?",
        "A1": "New Jersey Devils",
        "A2": "Arizona Coyotes",
        "A3": "Dallas Stars",
        "A4": "Florida panthers",
        "Answer": "New Jersey Devils"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who was the first winner of the Art Ross Trophy?",
        "A1": "Elmer Lach",
        "A2": "Dickie Moore",
        "A3": "Ted Lindsay",
        "A4": "Gordie Howe",
        "Answer": "Elmer Lach"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which player has won the Conn Smythe Trophy the most times?",
        "A1": "Patrick Roy",
        "A2": "Steve Yzerman",
        "A3": "Scott Stevens",
        "A4": "Mario Lemieux",
        "Answer": "Patrick Roy"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who is the only NHL player to win the Conn Smythe Trophy before winning the Calder Trophy as rookie of the year?",
        "A1": "Ken Dryden",
        "A2": "Butch Goring",
        "A3": "Glenn Hall",
        "A4": "Mike Bossy",
        "Answer": "Ken Dryden"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The Art Ross Trophy was presented to the NHL in 1947 by Arthur Howey 'Art' Ross. Who was he the General Manager of?",
        "A1": "Boston Bruins",
        "A2": "Philadelphia Flyers",
        "A3": "New York Rangers",
        "A4": "Montreal Canadiens",
        "Answer": "Boston Bruins"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is it called when a puck is dropped after a stoppage of play?",
        "A1": "Faceoff",
        "A2": "Tip-off",
        "A3": "Puck Drop",
        "A4": "Puck Toss",
        "Answer": "Faceoff"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which team has won the most Stanley Cups?",
        "A1": "Montreal Canadiens",
        "A2": "Detroit Red Wings",
        "A3": "Boston Bruins",
        "A4": "Toronto Maple Leafs",
        "Answer": "Montreal Canadiens"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who was the first NHL player to score more than 50 goals in a season?",
        "A1": "Bobby Hull",
        "A2": "Maurice Richard",
        "A3": "Bernie Geoffrion",
        "A4": "Wayne Gretzky",
        "Answer": "Bobby Hull"
    },
    {
        "Question": "When is high-sticking a double minor penalty?",
        "A1": "When blood is drawn",
        "A2": "When a bone is broken",
        "A3": "When a stick is broken",
        "A4": "When a tooth is knocked out",
        "Answer": "When blood is drawn"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many referees are on the ice at a time?",
        "A1": "1",
        "A2": "2",
        "A3": "3",
        "A4": "4",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many linesmen are on the ice at one time?",
        "A1": "1",
        "A2": "2",
        "A3": "3",
        "A4": "4",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many forwards are usually on the bench?",
        "A1": "10",
        "A2": "12",
        "A3": "8",
        "A4": "9",
        "Answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many minutes is a double minor penalty?",
        "A1": "2",
        "A2": "4",
        "A3": "5",
        "A4": "10",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many minutes are in each period?",
        "A1": "17",
        "A2": "20",
        "A3": "15",
        "A4": "12",
        "Answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The most goals scored in an NHL season is by Wayne Gretzky in the 1981/82 season. How many were there?",
        "A1": "88",
        "A2": "92",
        "A3": "73",
        "A4": "96",
        "Answer": "92"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What year was Wayne Gretzky traded to the Los Angeles Kings?",
        "A1": "1990",
        "A2": "1988",
        "A3": "1987",
        "A4": "1989",
        "Answer": "1988"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many points did Wayne Gretzky have?",
        "A1": "1,987",
        "A2": "2,857",
        "A3": "2,564",
        "A4": "3,274",
        "Answer": "2,857"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the maximum height the blade of a hockey stick can be?",
        "A1": "2 3/4 in",
        "A2": "3 in",
        "A3": "3 1/4 in",
        "A4": "2 7/8 in",
        "Answer": "3 in"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In the 85â€“86 season, the NHL Board made a decision to introduce offsetting penalties. What was this rule called?",
        "A1": "Offset Rule",
        "A2": "Gretzky Rule",
        "A3": "Coincidental Rule",
        "A4": "86er Rule",
        "Answer": "Gretzky Rule"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Every division has 8 teams except...",
        "A1": "Metropolitan",
        "A2": "Central",
        "A3": "Pacific",
        "A4": "Atlantic",
        "Answer": "Central"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What team did the Colorado Rockies become?",
        "A1": "Calgary Flames",
        "A2": "New Jersey Devils",
        "A3": "Colorado Avalanche",
        "A4": "Carolina Hurricanes",
        "Answer": "New Jersey Devils"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which team won their first Stanley Cup playoff series in 2018?",
        "A1": "Minnesota Wild",
        "A2": "Winnipeg Jets",
        "A3": "Carolina Hurricanes",
        "A4": "Columbus Blue Jackets",
        "Answer": "Winnipeg Jets"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What trophy goes to the MVP of the playoffs?",
        "A1": "Super Bowl",
        "A2": "Conn Smythe",
        "A3": "Stanley Cup",
        "A4": "Commissioner's Trophy",
        "Answer": "Conn Smythe"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who was drafted in the 2005 'Sweepstakes'?",
        "A1": "Alex Ovechkin",
        "A2": "Sidney Crosby",
        "A3": "Auston Matthews",
        "A4": "Conner McDavid",
        "Answer": "Sidney Crosby"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which player has won the most Stanley Cups?",
        "A1": "Mark Messier",
        "A2": "Henri Richard",
        "A3": "Ted Harris",
        "A4": "Dick Duff",
        "Answer": "Henri Richard"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who is the oldest active NHL player?",
        "A1": "Jaromir Jagr",
        "A2": "Matt Cullen",
        "A3": "Sidney Crosby",
        "A4": "Joe Thornton",
        "Answer": "Matt Cullen"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who was 'Mr Hockey'?",
        "A1": "Brett Hull",
        "A2": "Gordie Howe",
        "A3": "Mario Lemieux",
        "A4": "Mark Messier",
        "Answer": "Gordie Howe"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is it called when a puck goes in the net?",
        "A1": "Score",
        "A2": "Goal",
        "A3": "Touchdown",
        "A4": "Net",
        "Answer": "Goal"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What team is the newest addition to the NHL?",
        "A1": "Washington Capitals",
        "A2": "Vegas Golden Knights",
        "A3": "Dallas Stars",
        "A4": "New York Rangers",
        "Answer": "Vegas Golden Knights"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who is the only skater to win the Conn Smythe Trophy in a losing cause? Hint: It was won in 1976.",
        "A1": "Mike Bossy",
        "A2": "Reggie Leach",
        "A3": "Glenn Hall",
        "A4": "Roger Crozier",
        "Answer": "Reggie Leach"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What city will be getting a hockey team in 2021?",
        "A1": "Boise",
        "A2": "Seattle",
        "A3": "Kansas City",
        "A4": "Stockton",
        "Answer": "Seattle"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many periods are there in a hockey game?",
        "A1": "1",
        "A2": "2",
        "A3": "3",
        "A4": "4",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many Stanley Cups did Wayne Gretzky win?",
        "A1": "3",
        "A2": "6",
        "A3": "4",
        "A4": "5",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many players are on the ice during overtime in the regular season?",
        "A1": "2",
        "A2": "3",
        "A3": "4",
        "A4": "5",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many players are on the ice at one time?",
        "A1": "4",
        "A2": "5",
        "A3": "6",
        "A4": "7",
        "Answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many teams did the NHL start out with?",
        "A1": "2",
        "A2": "4",
        "A3": "6",
        "A4": "8",
        "Answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many minutes is a major penalty?",
        "A1": "2",
        "A2": "4",
        "A3": "5",
        "A4": "10",
        "Answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many players are allowed on the bench?",
        "A1": "10",
        "A2": "15",
        "A3": "20",
        "A4": "22",
        "Answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many teams in the NHL are based in USA?",
        "A1": "22",
        "A2": "23",
        "A3": "24",
        "A4": "25",
        "Answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many teams are in the NHL?",
        "A1": "25",
        "A2": "30",
        "A3": "31",
        "A4": "35",
        "Answer": "31"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many years has the NHL been around?",
        "A1": "102",
        "A2": "103",
        "A3": "101",
        "A4": "112",
        "Answer": "102"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What year was Eric Lindros drafted?",
        "A1": "1992",
        "A2": "1990",
        "A3": "1991",
        "A4": "1989",
        "Answer": "1991"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the minimum hight a player's numbers must be on the back of his sweater?",
        "A1": "8 in",
        "A2": "6 in",
        "A3": "10 in",
        "A4": "12 in",
        "Answer": "10 in"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How long is it from blue line to blue line?",
        "A1": "60 ft",
        "A2": "55 ft",
        "A3": "50 ft",
        "A4": "65 ft",
        "Answer": "50 ft"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who is second in all time NHL points?",
        "A1": "Gordie Howe",
        "A2": "Mario Lemieux",
        "A3": "Jaromir Jagr",
        "A4": "Bobby Orr",
        "Answer": "Jaromir Jagr"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the trophy called that is won at the end of the final championship?",
        "A1": "Super Bowl",
        "A2": "Conn Smythe",
        "A3": "Stanley Cup",
        "A4": "Commissioner's Trophy",
        "Answer": "Stanley Cup"
    },
    {
        "Question": "If two teams are tied in points at the end of the regular season, what is used to determine who is first?",
        "A1": "GF",
        "A2": "DIFF",
        "A3": "ROW",
        "A4": "GA",
        "Answer": "ROW"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The act of throwing the body, from any direction, across or below the knees of an opponent is called...",
        "A1": "Physical Foul",
        "A2": "Charging",
        "A3": "Clipping",
        "A4": "Knee Chopping",
        "Answer": "Clipping"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The Conn Smythe Trophy has been won sixteen times by goaltenders. What other position has won it sixteen times?",
        "A1": "Right Wingers",
        "A2": "Defensemen",
        "A3": "Centers",
        "A4": "Left Wingers",
        "Answer": "Centers"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Out of these teams, who has never won a Stanley Cup?",
        "A1": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
        "A2": "New York Islanders",
        "A3": "Vancouver Canucks",
        "A4": "Los Angeles Kings",
        "Answer": "Vancouver Canucks"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who is the youngest captain ever to hoist the Stanley Cup?",
        "A1": "Alex Ovechkin",
        "A2": "Wayne Gretzky",
        "A3": "Sidney Crosby",
        "A4": "Mario Lemieux",
        "Answer": "Sidney Crosby"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Why wasn't there a draft in 2004?",
        "A1": "Not enough players",
        "A2": "Not enough money",
        "A3": "Lockout",
        "A4": "Teams voted against it",
        "Answer": "Lockout"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In the regular season, what happens if overtime results in a tie score?",
        "A1": "Game ends tied",
        "A2": "Another overtime",
        "A3": "Shootout",
        "A4": "They toss a coin",
        "Answer": "Shootout"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which team has the lowest point percentage in NHL history?",
        "A1": "Carolina Hurricanes",
        "A2": "Columbus Blue Jackets",
        "A3": "Arizona Coyotes",
        "A4": "Vancouver Canucks",
        "Answer": "Arizona Coyotes"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many Alternate Captains can a team have when the Captain is not dressed for a game?",
        "A1": "1",
        "A2": "4",
        "A3": "2",
        "A4": "3",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many players are on the ice during overtime in the playoffs?",
        "A1": "3",
        "A2": "4",
        "A3": "5",
        "A4": "6",
        "Answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many teams in the NHL are based in the Canada?",
        "A1": "6",
        "A2": "5",
        "A3": "8",
        "A4": "7",
        "Answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many defunct and relocated teams in the NHL are there?",
        "A1": "10",
        "A2": "5",
        "A3": "16",
        "A4": "19",
        "Answer": "19"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many different hand signals does a referee make?",
        "A1": "20",
        "A2": "10",
        "A3": "15",
        "A4": "30",
        "Answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How heavy is an NHL hockey puck?",
        "A1": "3oz",
        "A2": "4oz",
        "A3": "5oz",
        "A4": "6oz",
        "Answer": "6oz"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What happened at the first ever hockey game that exists in todays game?",
        "A1": "Beer was served",
        "A2": "Three pucks were used",
        "A3": "There was 4 periods",
        "A4": "A fight broke out",
        "Answer": "A fight broke out"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What player is known as 'The Golden Jet'?",
        "A1": "Mark Messier",
        "A2": "Bobby Orr",
        "A3": "Jeff Skinner",
        "A4": "Bobby Hull",
        "Answer": "Bobby Hull"
    },
    {
        "Question": "The Stockton Heat play in Stockton, CA. Who is their NHL affiliate?",
        "A1": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
        "A2": "New Jersey Devils",
        "A3": "Florida Panthers",
        "A4": "Calgary Flames",
        "Answer": "Calgary Flames"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is Vancouver's team name?",
        "A1": "Stars",
        "A2": "Sabers",
        "A3": "Oilers",
        "A4": "Canucks",
        "Answer": "Canucks"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which team in 1976 merged with the Minnesota North Stars, who are currently the Dallas Stars?",
        "A1": "Philadelphia Quakers",
        "A2": "Kansas City Scouts",
        "A3": "Atlanta Flames",
        "A4": "Cleveland Barons",
        "Answer": "Cleveland Barons"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who was the oldest player to win the Art Ross Trophy?",
        "A1": "Wayne Gretzky",
        "A2": "Jaromir Jagr",
        "A3": "Eric Lindros",
        "A4": "Martin St. Louis",
        "Answer": "Martin St. Louis"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What team did Wayne Gretzky retire with?",
        "A1": "Los Angeles Kings",
        "A2": "St. Louis Blues",
        "A3": "Edmonton Oilers",
        "A4": "New York Rangers",
        "Answer": "New York Rangers"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What player is known as 'Houdini'?",
        "A1": "Patrick Kane",
        "A2": "Wayne Gretzky",
        "A3": "Peter Forsberg",
        "A4": "Pavel Datsyuk",
        "Answer": "Pavel Datsyuk"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who is the only teenager ever to win the Art Ross trophy?",
        "A1": "Alex Ovechkin",
        "A2": "Wayne Gretzky",
        "A3": "Mario Lemieux",
        "A4": "Sidney Crosby",
        "Answer": "Sidney Crosby"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What frozen substance is hockey played on?",
        "A1": "Plastic",
        "A2": "Ice",
        "A3": "Concrete",
        "A4": "Water",
        "Answer": "Water"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who is the 'Great One'?",
        "A1": "Sidney Crosby",
        "A2": "Brett Hull",
        "A3": "Mario Lemieux",
        "A4": "Wayne Gretzky",
        "Answer": "Wayne Gretzky"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who is only defenseman to win the Conn Smythe Trophy twice?",
        "A1": "Fredrik Olausson",
        "A2": "Bobby Orr",
        "A3": "Aubrey Clapper",
        "A4": "Lionel Conacher",
        "Answer": "Bobby Orr"
    }
]